synthasite.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy | Yola.com

Effective Date: 25 May 2018

Welcome to Yola’s Privacy Policy! We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of our users. Please familiarize yourself with the contents of this policy in order to understand how we handle customer data and what your rights and responsibilities are as a user of our service. 

##  1\. Your Consent (please read carefully!) 

This privacy policy (“Policy”) explains how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by Yola, Inc., with respect to your use of the website located at www.yola.com (the “Site”) so you can make an informed decision about using the Site and the website creation and hosting services offered by Yola. 

Please note that this Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible in any manner for, any information you provide to third parties in connection with websites hosted by Yola (“User Sites”) or how the third parties who operate such User Sites may use the personal information you provide to them. Such information is subject to the privacy practices of such User Site, and we encourage you to become familiar with their privacy practices before disclosing information directly to them. 

This Privacy Policy constitutes a binding and enforceable legal contract between Yola and you — so please read it carefully! 

You may visit and/or use the Services (as defined in the Terms of Service) only if you fully agree to this Privacy Policy — and by accessing and/or using any of the Services, you signify and affirm your informed consent to this Privacy Policy, including to the collection and processing of your Personal Information as defined and explained below. 

**Please note:** you are not obligated by law to provide us with any information. You hereby acknowledge, warrant and agree that any information you do provide us is provided of your own free will and consent, for the purposes and uses described herein. 

## The Short Version

This policy describes our privacy practices — what information we collect on our visitors and users, how we collect it, what we do with it, how we protect it, and your rights regarding your information. This privacy policy does not cover third party sites hosted by Yola that you may visit and you need to approach the site owners directly for any questions on their privacy policies. 

By accessing or using any of our services, you consent to this Privacy Policy. You may use our services only if you fully consent to the practices described in this policy. 

## 2\. What Information Do We Collect?

### 2.1. Visitor and User Information

We collect two basic types of information with our service, namely personal information and aggregate information. 

### Personal Information

As used herein, the term “personal information” means information that specifically identifies an individual. The Personal Information collected by us mainly consists of contact details (e.g., e-mail address or phone number), billing details (name, physical billing address, payment method, and transaction details), details regarding a browsing or usage session (IP address, and Geo-location), details regarding connected third-party accounts (such as the e-mail or username for a connected PayPal, Google or Facebook account), scanned identification documents provided to us (such as an ID card, driver’s license, passport or official company registration documents), correspondences (including those made through or uploaded to our Services), and any other Personal Information provided to us by Visitors and/or Users through their access to and/or use of the Services. Our definition of personal information does not include “aggregate” information (see below). 

### Aggregate Information

Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of services or users from which individual user identities have been removed. In other words, information on how you use our service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the service, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Aggregate information helps us understand trends in our users’ needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor our service. This policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information, and we may share aggregate information about our users with third parties for various purposes, including to help us better understand and improve our service, and for advertising and marketing purposes. 

### 2.2. Users of Users Information

We may also collect similar information pertaining to visitors of our User’s Websites or Services (“Users-of-Users”), on our Users’ behalf (as further described in Section 6 below). This data is aggregated for our use and for sharing with third parties as described above. 

### 2.3. Yola Jobs Applicant Information

We also collect information that is provided to us by Yola jobs candidates (“Applicants”), when they apply to any of the open positions published at https://www.yola.com/about-us/jobs, by e-mail or otherwise (as further described in Section 7 below). 

## The Short Version

We collect two types of information: **Personal Information** (which could be used to uniquely identify an individual) and **Aggregate Information** (which is non-identifying). 

We collect such information regarding our users and visitors, our users’ visitors, job applicants and anyone else who may provide it to us. 

##  3\. How Do We Collect Such Information? 

### Active Collection

Personal information may be collected in a number of ways when you visit our Site. We may collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us which may contain personal information. For example, we may collect your name, address, email address, and other contact and demographic information when you register and set up an account or contact us by e-mail or other means. We may also collect payment information if applicable. In addition, from time to time we may collect demographic, contact or other personal information you voluntarily provide to us, such as in connection with your participation in surveys, sweepstakes, contests, games, promotional offers, and other activities on the Site. 

For each visit of registered user of the Site (each a “Registered User”) to the Yola website, our Web server automatically recognizes any header information that is shared with our Web server. Yola collects the IP address and header information, and may collect the following: 

  * The e-mail address of Registered Users of our Site and the Yola Toolset (as defined in our Terms of Service), so that we and our partners may communicate with Registered Users. 
  * The e-mail addresses of Registered Users who communicate with us via e-mail, and/or make postings to our chat areas. 
  * Aggregate information on what pages Registered Users access or visit. 
  * Registered User-specific information on what pages Registered Users access or visit. 
  * Personal information may also be collected if you leave comments or other communications on the Site, such as on the chat areas, and/or send email directly to Yola. 

By doing so your name and the content of your communication may be made public and can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

### Automatically Collected Information

As mentioned above, we automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you use the website, our systems may automatically collect your IP address and the type of operating system or browser you use. We may also collect information pertaining to your account activity, and standard access information, such as the time and date of your accessing the service and your usage of the service. We use such information for purposes such as compiling aggregated statistics about service usage, developing new features, and improving our services. 

We may also use cookie technology to collect information. See Section 9 for details. 

## The Short Version

When you visit or use our services — you may also provide us with certain information either automatically through your uses, or by manually submitting it. 

We use cookise to identify you to our Services. 

## 4\. Why Do We Collect Such Information?

We collect such Non-personal and Personal Information for the following purposes: 

  * To provide and operate the Services; 
  * To further develop, customize and improve our Services, based on Visitors’ and Users’ common or personal preferences, experiences and difficulties; 
  * To provide our Users with ongoing customer assistance and technical support; 
  * To be able to contact our Visitors and Users with general or personalized service-related notices and promotional messages (as further detailed in Section 11 below); 
  * To facilitate, sponsor and offer certain contests, events and promotions, determine participants’ eligibility, monitor performance, contact winners and grant prizes and benefits; 
  * To create aggregated statistical data and other aggregated and/or inferred Non-personal Information, which we or our business partners may use to provide and improve our respective services; 
  * To enhance our data security and fraud prevention capabilities; 
  * To consider Applicants’ candidacy for working at Yola (as further detailed in Section 7 below); and 
  * To comply with any applicable laws and regulations. 

## The Short Version

We collect and use information in order to provide our services and make them better and safer. 

We also collect and use information in order to contact our visitors, users and job applicants, and in order to comply with the laws applicable to us. 

##  5\. Where Do We Store Your Information? 

Yola Visitors’, Yola Users’ and Users-of-Users’ Personal Information may be maintained, processed and stored by Yola and our authorized affiliates and service providers in the United States of America. Yola and all US-based sub-processors comply with the EU–US privacy shield. We have employees in the US, Canada, Australia, Ukraine, and South Africa who have access to customer data. 

Yola Jobs Applicants Information will be maintained, processed and stored in the United States, South Africa and Ukraine, in the applied position’s location(s), and as necessary, in secured cloud storage provided by our Third Party Services. Yola.com is based in the United States, and we operate under the EU–US and Swiss–US Privacy Shield Frameworks. 

Yola affiliates and service providers that store or process your Personal Information on Yola’s behalf are each committed to keep it protected and secured, in accordance with industry standards and regardless of any lesser legal requirements which may apply in their jurisdiction. 

###  5.1. EU–US and Swiss–US Privacy Shield Frameworks 

Yola complies with the EU–US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss–US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from the European Union and Switzerland and the United States, respectively. Yola has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>. 

In compliance with the EU–US and Swiss–US Privacy Shield Principles, Yola commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Yola by email at [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com). 

Upon request Yola will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by contacting us at [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com). We will respond to your request within 30 days. 

Yola has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU–US and Swiss–US Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [ http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ ](https://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint. 

Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel. 

Yola may also be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

Yola is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). 

## The Short Version

We may store and process Personal Information subject to this policy in the USA, whether by ourselves or with the help of our affiliates and service providers. 

Yola’s data storage providers are committed to protect and secure your data. Among other things, Yola adheres to the EU–US & Swiss–US Privacy Shield Principles, for further protecting and enhancing our users’ privacy. 

## 6\. Users-of-Users’ Information

Yola may collect, store and process certain Aggregated and Personal Information of Users-of-Users (“Users-of-Users Information”), on our Users’ behalf. For example we act as a data processor for responses sent via the Yola Form widget, and also for Online Store customer registrations and orders. Such contacts are then stored with Yola, on the User’s behalf. Yola will aggregate this data (as in Section 2.1 above) to help us understand and respond to users’ needs. 

For such purposes, Yola serves and shall be considered as a “Data Processor” and not as the “Controller” (as both such capitalized terms are defined in the European Data Protection Directive) of such Users-of-Users Information. The Users controlling and operating such User Websites shall be considered as the “Controllers” of such Users-of-Users Information, and are responsible for complying with all laws and regulations that may apply to the collection and control of such Users-of-Users Information, including all privacy and data protection laws of all relevant jurisdictions. You are responsible for the security, integrity and authorized usage of your Users-of-Users’ Personal Information, and for obtaining any consents and permissions required for the collection and usage of such information. 

Yola cannot provide legal advice to Users or their Users-of-Users, however we do recommend that all Users publish and maintain clear and comprehensive privacy policies on their User Websites, in accordance with the applicable laws and regulations, and that all Users-of-Users carefully read those policies and make sure that they consent to them. 

For more information on how Users-of-Users Information may be handled by Yola (which may be relevant for the specific notice you provide to and/or consent you obtain from your Users-of-Users), please see Sections 8, 13 and 14 below. 

If you are a visitor, user or customer of any of our Users, please read the following: Yola has no direct relationship with the individual Users-of-Users whose Personal Information it processes. If you are a visitor, user or customer of any of our Users, and would like to make any requests or queries regarding your Personal Information, please contact such User(s) directly. For example, if you wish to access, correct, amend, or delete inaccurate information processed by Yola on behalf of its Users, please direct your query to the relevant User (who is the “Controller” of such data). If requested to remove any Users-of-Users’ Personal Information, we will respond to such request within thirty (30) days. Unless otherwise instructed by our User, we will retain their Users-of-Users’ Personal Information for the period set forth in Section 13 below. 

## The Short Version

Yola may collect and process information regarding the users of our users. We do this on our users’ behalf. Our users are solely responsible for their users-of-users information, including for its legality, security and integrity. 

Yola has no direct relationship with any of its users’ users. If you are a user-of-user, please contact such user directly. 

## 7\. Yola Jobs Applications

Yola welcomes all qualified Applicants to apply to any of the open positions published at https://www.yola.com/about-us/jobs, by sending us their contact details and CV (“Applicants Information”) via the relevant Position Application Form on our Site, or through any other means provided by us. 

We understand that privacy and discretion are crucial to our Applicants, and are committed to keep Applicants’ Information private and use it solely for Yola’s internal recruitment purposes (including for identifying Applicants, evaluating their applications, making hiring and employment decisions, and contacting Applicants by phone or in writing). 

Please note that Yola may retain Applicants’ Information submitted to it even after the applied position has been filled or closed. This is done so we could re-consider Applicants for other positions and opportunities at Yola; so we could use their Applicants’ Information as reference for future applications submitted by them; and in case the Applicant is hired, for additional employment and business purposes related to his/her work at Yola. 

If you previously submitted your Applicants Information to Yola, and now wish to access it, update it or have it deleted from Yola’s systems, please contact us at [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com). 

## The Short Version

We welcome all qualified job seekers to apply to any of our open positions, by sending us their contact details and CV. We will use such information solely for our internal recruitment, employment and business purposes. 

##  8\. Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties 

Yola may share your Personal Information with third parties (or otherwise allow them access to it) only in the following manners and instances: 

### 8.1. Third Party Services

Yola has partnered with a number of selected service providers, whose services and solutions complement, facilitate and enhance our own. These include service providers, hosting and server co-location services, communications and content delivery networks (CDNs), billing and payment processing services, domain name registrars, fraud detection and prevention services, web and service analytics, e-mail distribution and monitoring services, session recording, performance measurement data optimization and marketing services, customer service outsourcing, content providers, and our legal and financial advisors (collectively, “Third Party Service(s)”). 

Such Third Party Services may receive or otherwise have access to our Visitors’ and Users’ Personal Information and/or Users-of-Users’ Personal Information, in its entirety or in part — depending on each of their particular roles and purposes in facilitating and enhancing our Services and business, and may only use it for such purposes. 

Note that while our Services may contain links to other websites or services, we are not responsible for such websites’ or services’ privacy practices, and encourage you to be aware when you leave our Services and read the privacy statements of each and every website and service you visit. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such linked third-party websites and services. 

Yola is accountable for personal data that it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party as described in the Privacy Shield Principles. In particular, Yola remains responsible and liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if third-party agents that it engages to process the personal data on its behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless Yola proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage. 

###  8.2. Law Enforcement, Legal Requests and Duties 

Yola may disclose or otherwise allow others access to your Personal Information pursuant to a legal request, such as a subpoena, legal proceedings, search warrant or court order, or in compliance with applicable laws, if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so, with or without notice to you. 

### 8.3. Protecting Rights and Safety

Yola may share your Personal Information with others if we believe in good faith that this will help protect the rights, property or personal safety of Yola, any of our Users, any Users-of-Users, or any member of the general public, with or without notice to you. 

###  8.4. Social Media Features and Framed Pages 

Our Services include certain Social Media features and widgets, such as the “Facebook Connect” or “Google Sign-in” features, “Facebook Like” button, the “Share this” button or other interactive mini-programs (“Social Media Features”). These Social Media Features may collect information such as your IP address or which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable them to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with these third parties are governed by their policies and not ours. 

In addition, our Services may enable you to share your Personal Information with third parties directly, such as via page framing techniques to serve content to or from Third Party Services or other parties, while preserving the look and feel of our Site and Services (“Frames”). Please be aware that if you choose to interact or share any Personal Information via such Frames, you are in fact providing it to these third parties and not to us, and such interactions and sharing too are governed by such third parties’ policies and not ours. 

###  8.5. Yola Subsidiaries and Affiliated Companies 

We may share Personal Information internally within our family of companies, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may share your Personal Information with co-owned affiliates which employ Yola employees in the US, Ukraine and South Africa, in the course of facilitating and providing you (and your Users-of-Users) with our Services. In addition, should Yola or any of its affiliates undergo any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of substantially all of its assets, your Personal Information may be shared with the parties involved in such event. If we have a good faith belief that such change in control might materially affect your Personal Information then stored with us, we will notify you via e-mail and/or prominent notice on our Site of this event and certain choices you may have regarding your Personal Information. Sharing of Personal Information from Yola subsidiaries and affiliated companies in the European Union and Switzerland to Yola’s United States subsidiary, adheres to the EU–US and Swiss–US Privacy Shield frameworks. 

For the avoidance of doubt, Yola may share your Personal Information in manners other than as described above, pursuant to your explicit approval, or if we are legally obligated to do so. Moreover, Yola may transfer, share, disclose or otherwise use Non-personal Information in its sole discretion and without the need for further approval. 

In the event that Yola transfers your personal information to a third party that is acting as an agent, Yola will enter into a written agreement with such third party requiring that the third party provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the relevant principles, and also requiring that personal data is only processed for limited and specified purposes. 

## The Short Version

We may share the information of our visitors, users and their users-of-users with various third parties, including certain service providers, law enforcement officials and application developers. The information may be shared solely in accordance with this policy. 

##  9\. Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies 

Yola, together with its marketing, analytics and technology partners, uses certain monitoring and tracking technologies (such as cookies, beacons, pixels, tags and scripts). These technologies are used in order to maintain, provide and improve our Services on an ongoing basis, and in order to provide our Visitors, our Users and their Users-of-Users with a better experience. For example, thanks to these technologies, we are able to maintain and keep track of our Visitors’ and Users’ preferences and authenticated sessions, to better secure our Services, to identify technical issues, user trends and effectiveness of campaigns, and to monitor and improve the overall performance of our Services. 

The use of cookies by our partners and affiliates is not covered by our Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our affiliates may use session ID cookies on their websites to give you access to Yola discounts and promotions. Our integration partners use cookies within Yola in order for you to use the parts of the Yola Toolset that are implemented by these partners. 

If you want to delete or block any cookies, please refer to the help and support area on your internet browser for instructions on how to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. Information on deleting or controlling cookies is also available at <https://www.aboutcookies.org/> (note that this website is not provided by Yola, and we therefore cannot ensure its accuracy, completeness or availability). Please note that deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies or tracking technologies may prevent you from accessing certain areas or features of our Services, or may otherwise adversely affect your user experience. 

### Third Party Analytics Services

Some parts of our Service use third party analyticservices to help us create a better user experience. 

  * Google Analytics. You can opt-out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) and installing the add-on for your specific browser. 
  * Mixpanel. You can opt-out of Mixpanel’s analytics service at [Mixpanel Opt Out](https://mixpanel.com/optout/). 
  * Fullstory.com. You can opt-out of FullStory’s analytics service at [FullStory Opt Out](https://www.fullstory.com/optout/). 

Javascript tracking: We and certain Third Party Services may employ tracking, which enables them and us to improve our Services by measuring their effectiveness and performance. 

Behavioral Targeting/Re-Targeting: Certain Third Party Services and ad networks may display advertising on our service. Such parties may use certain tracking technologies to collect certain information about your activities on the Services and different third party Services to provide you with targeted advertising based on your interests and preferences. You may opt-out of receiving targeted ads from certain advertisers and ad networks by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if you are located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) (provided by YourChoicesOnline.eu). Please note this does not opt you out of receiving any advertising. 

“Do Not Track” Signals: Please note that we do not change our practices in response to a “Do Not Track” signal in the HTTP header from a browser or mobile application. 

## The Short Version

We and certain third party services may use cookies and similar tracking technologies throughout our services. 

These technologies are used mostly for stability, security, functionality, performance and advertising purposes. 

You may block, opt-out of or otherwise manage such tracking technologies by yourself, through your browser settings or other sources — but please note that this may adversely affect the way you experience our services. 

### 10\. Information about Children

Our service is not intended to be used by children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children except in compliance with applicable law. 

Our Terms of Service bar children from using our services. 

## 11\. Communications from Yola

### 11.1. Promotional Messages

We will communicate with you via email. Yola intends to send regular email updates and occasional promotional offers that may be of interest to you. You may opt-out of these mailings at any time. If you do not want to receive marketing and promotional e-mails from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an e-mail to [support@yola.com](mailto:support@yola.com) or follow the unsubscribe instructions that are included in each email communication. 

This will not prevent us from sending you operational, account related or other non-marketing emails. If you wish to no longer receive these emails please deactivate your account by clicking on the Profile link after you log in and then clicking the Delete Account link at the bottom of the page. Alternatively, you can email our Customer Support at [support@yola.com](mailto:support@yola.com). 

## The Short Version

You agree that we or our partners may send you promotional messages and content. You can easily opt-out of receiving promotional messages by contacting us or using the “unsubscribe” options provided by us. 

### 11.2. Service and Billing Messages

Yola may also contact you with important information regarding our Services, or your use thereof. 

Opting out of promotional messages will not prevent us from sending you operational, account related or other non-marketing emails. If you wish to no longer receive these emails please deactivate your account by clicking on the Profile link after you log in and then clicking the Delete Account link at the bottom of the page. Alternatively, you can email our Customer Support at [support@yola.com](mailto:support@yola.com). 

We may also contact you with service and billing-related messages and content. You will not be able to opt-out of receiving such messages. 

## 12\. Accessing Your Personal Information

If you wish to access and/or request us to make corrections to the Personal Information that you have stored with us (either yours or your Users-of-Users’), or wish to request a list of what Personal Information (if any) pertaining to you we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes, feel free to send us an e-mail to [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com) or mail your request to Yola.com, 548 Market Street #38798, San Francisco, CA 94104-5401, USA, and we will respond within a reasonable timeframe and in accordance with any applicable law. Please note that you will be asked to verify your identity in order to ensure that an unauthorized person is not attempting to exploit your rights in order to access your data. 

You have the right to access your personal information. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update your profile or delete it by clicking on the Profile link after you log in and then clicking the Delete Account link at the bottom of the page. Alternatively, you can email our Customer Support at [support@yola.com](mailto:support@yola.com). If you would like your personal data permanently deleted, please email [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com). 

## The Short Version

You may request to access or correct the personal information you have stored with us, by sending us an e-mail or letter. You may also correct, update or remove certain information, or deactivate your account, through your account or website settings. We will respond to your request within 30 days. Proof of identity will be required for your protection and ours. 

## 13\. Data Retention

We retain your Personal Information (as well as your Users-of-Users Information) as needed to provide you with our Services. 

We may continue to retain such Personal Information even after you deactivate your User Account and/or cease to use any particular Services, as reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes regarding our Users or their Users-of-Users, prevent fraud and abuse, enforce our agreements and/or protect our legitimate interests. For permanent deletion of your data please email [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com). 

## The Short Version

We may keep your information for as long needed (for example, if we are legally obligated to keep it further, or need it to protect our interests). You have the right to request permanent deletion of your data, which can be done by emailing [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com). 

## 14\. Security

Yola has implemented security measures designed to protect the Personal Information you share with us, including physical, electronic and procedural measures. Among other things, we offer HTTPS secure access to all areas on our Services; the transmission of sensitive payment information (such as a credit card number) through our designated purchase forms is protected by an industry standard SSL/TLS encrypted connection; and we regularly maintain a PCI DSS (Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards) certification. We also regularly monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks, and regularly seek new ways and Third Party Services for further enhancing the security of our Services and protection of our Visitors’ and Users’ privacy. 

However — regardless of the measures and efforts taken by Yola, we cannot and do not guarantee the absolute protection and security of your Personal Information, your Users-of-Users’ Information or any other User Content you upload, publish or otherwise share with Yola or anyone else. 

We therefore encourage you to set strong passwords for your User Account and User Website, and avoid providing us with any sensitive information which you believe its disclosure could cause you substantial or irreparable harm. Furthermore, e-mail and instant messaging are not recognized as secure forms of communications, we request and encourage you not to share any Personal Information on any of these areas or via any of these methods. 

### Hosted websites

Users publishing websites to a free subdomain or a custom domain managed by Yola, will be provided with DDoS protection and DNS management capabilities. Yola uses CloudFlare to provide DDoS protection and DNS services for the Yola Toolset, Yola Site and customer websites. A copy of CloudFlare’s privacy policy is available [here](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/). 

We use reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized release of or access to your personal data. However, we cannot guarantee that your information will not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others. If Yola learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Yola may also post a notice on the Site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach, you should notify us at [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com). 

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number, national ID, personal health information) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Credit card details are stored in our Payment Gateway’s highly secure Payment Vault that is fully compliant with the Payment Card Industry’s Data Security Standards. 

If you have any questions regarding the security of our Services, you are more than welcome to contact us at [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com). 

## The Short Version

We are committed to securing your personal information, and use various security measures to better protect it. 

However, as we can’t guarantee absolute protection — we encourage you to be careful, set a strong password for your account, and avoid submitting any sensitive information which, if exposed, could cause you major harm. 

## 15\. Public Forums and User Content

Our Services offer publicly accessible blogs, communities and support forums. Be aware that any information you provide in any such areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your Personal Information from our blogs, communities or forums, feel free to contact us at: [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personal Information from such areas. For example, if you use a third party application to post a comment (e.g., the Facebook social plugin application) while logged in to your related profile with such third party, you will need to login into such application or contact its provider if you want to have the Personal Information you posted through it removed. 

In any event, we recommend that you do not post any information (or use any posting means to post information) you would not want to be made public on these areas. 

If you upload any User Content to your User Account or post it on your User Website and provide it in any other way as part of the use of any Service, you do so at your own risk. 

We cannot control the actions of other Users or members of the public who may access your User Content, and are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures you or we may have placed on your User Website (including, for instance, password-protected areas on your User Website). You understand and acknowledge that, even after its removal by you or us, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if any third parties (including any of your Users-of-Users) have copied or stored such User Content. Again, we recommend that you do not upload or post any information you would not want to be publicly available. 

## The Short Version

Please avoid posting any information to any of the public areas on our Services, or to your own website, if you don’t want it to become publicly available. 

##  16\. Terms of Service, Updates and Interpretation 

Your use of any of our Services, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Service and all of its general provisions including disclaimer of warranty, limitation of liability and indemnity. 

This Privacy Policy, its interpretation, and any claims and disputes related hereto, shall be governed by, construed under and enforced in all respects solely and exclusively in accordance with the internal substantive laws of the State of California, without respect to its conflict of laws principles. Any and all such claims and disputes shall be brought in, and you hereby consent to them being decided exclusively by, a court of competent jurisdiction located in the State of California in the USA. 

Yola may amend this Policy from time to time to remain consistent with the requirements of applicable legistlation and the EU–US and Swiss–US Privacy Shield programs. We will post any revised policy on this Site, and we will provide email and/or other notifications of any substantial changes. Your use of the Site after the revised Policy has been posted will constitute your consent to such revised Policy. If you are concerned about how your personal information is used, you should subscribe to our blog RSS feed at https://www.yola.com/blog/ or e-mail us at [support@yola.com](mailto:support@yola.com). This will not prevent Yola from using your personal information for the specific purposes for which it was collected. 

Our Postal Address is:

548 Market Street #38798, San Francisco, CA 94104-5401, USA 

We can be reached via e-mail at [support@yola.com](mailto:support@yola.com). 

Any heading, caption or section title contained herein, and any explanation or summary under the right “The Short Version” column, is provided only for convenience, and in no way defines or explains any section or provision hereof, or legally binds any of us in any way. 

If a translated (non-English) version of this Privacy Policy conflicts in any way with its English version, the provisions of the English version shall prevail. 

## The Short Version

As noted in our Terms of Service, we disclaim all warranties and shall not be liable for any damages (subject to applicable law). This policy shall be governed by the laws of the the State of California in the USA. 

Any disputes between us may only be brought before the courts of the State of California in the USA. We may change this policy at any time. We will notify you of any material changes. Only the left column is legally binding (this column is just for clarity). 

## 17\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@yola.com](mailto:privacy@yola.com). 

You may also contact us by mail at: 548 Market Street #38798, San Francisco, CA 94104-5401, USA. 

## The Short Version

As Have any questions or suggestions? We’d love to hear them!
